slidethecity.com 2014-09-21

# Slide the City - Privacy Policy

### Our Commitment to Privacy

Your privacy is important to us.

To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

### What information do we collect?

We collect information when you fill out your race registration, including your name, email, address, phone number, date of birth and payment details.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information collected may be used to improve our website, improve customer service, to process transactions, to send periodic emails with information about Slide The City race, to administer a contest, survey, promotion of other racing events or other site features. All credit card information will be used only to process the registration for the current registration purchased and will only be shared with those affiliated with processing the transaction and is not stored by The Slide The City.

We may also release information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. Non-personally identifiable information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Your email address will never be sold to outside affiliates.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information and all measures will be taken to protect this information.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

The online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Consent

By using our site and submitting your registration you hereby consent to the online privacy policy, as stated.

By submitting, posting or displaying any content, pictures and other materials on our facebook page, you grant to us a worldwide, non-exclusive, royalty-ree license (with the right to sublicense) to use, copy, reproduce, process, adapt, modify, publish, transmit, disply and distribute such content, pictures or other materials in any and all media, advertising, marketing or other distribution methods whether now known or later developed.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

Any changes made to this privacy policy will be noted on this page.

This policy was last modified on 6/11/2014

### Contact

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information listed below.

Slide The City  
info@slidethecity.com
